好的
Ok
我爱大蒜大蒜脸
I love garlic garlic face before
跳过这个
Skip this
尽量摇动
Shaking as hard as possible
皮肤刚脱落
The skin just comes off
这是什么
What is this
明天的shamwow家伙罗伯特
Robert the shamwow guy tomorrow about this
我的破掉
I broke
压蒜器
Garlic press
我妈妈是这个
My mum is this
幸运的是我很坚强
Luckily I'm very strong
让我感觉像中世纪医生
Makes me feel like and mediaeval doctors
权力的游戏我将半裸米兰达
Game of Thrones I'll be half naked Miranda
Gaelic实际上是用手指挖出的表皮
Gaelic is actually cuticles scooping out with your finger making food and getting
老师同时我也要加一点盐
Teacher at the same time I would also add a bit of salt to this
太空堡垒将其分解并像稠度一样粘贴
Battlestar breaking it down and giving it that paste like consistency
跳过
Skip
谁以为
Whoever thought
什么时候方便
What time in handy
好吧，我要去掉
Ok so I'm going to remove
关
Close
从头开始
From the head
我要做的第一件事是从底部挖根
First thing I do is cut the roots off of the bottom
甚至还没感觉到
Before you even feeling it
我只是要屈膝
I'm just going to take the side of my knee
那将把它从码头上释放
That will release it from the pier
做一个活塞只是为了给你一个快速粗暴的印章
For making a piston just gonna give you a quick rough chop
盐多少钱，我将在4中继续工作
How many is a little bit of salt and I'm just going to work my way back in 4
将大蒜分解
The song access for abrasive breaks the garlic down
我只是来回来回
I'm just going to come back and forth
我的意思是
I mean
Nuffield vampires tonight